{
    "id": "jackdoe",
    "name": "Jackdoe",
    "yomi": "ジャックドー",
    "text": [
        "私はJackdoeと申します。まだまだ駆け出しの身ですが、ミュージシャンをしています。<br>生まれてから今までの間、特に音楽を習うこともなく、ただ音楽が身近な場所にあったというだけの私ですが、そこから何故か自分で作りたいと思うようになり、ミュージシャンとして活動を始めるようになりました。",
        "I am an ordinary person who are not talented. I am fortunately gifted in making efforts and I know I don't give up easily. I have kept making extensive efforts until I could do what I wanted to do.<br/>Please make effort simply and honestly and please don't give up so that your dreams will come true. Your dreams will not come true when you give it up, I believe."
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "Twitter",
            "href": "https://www.twitter.com/John_yuuya/"
        },
        {
            "a": "SoundCloud",
            "href": "https://www.soundcloud.com/jackdoe-1/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Do you think there is a thing that more important than a life?",
            "jp": "命よりも大切ななにかがある",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "ない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Do you have a belief?",
            "jp": "誰に言われても曲げることのない信念がある",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "ない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "Do you like yourself?",
            "jp": "自分のことが好きかどうか",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "好き",
            "no": "No i don't like myself",
            "right": "嫌い"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Which do you like?",
            "jp": "夏と冬どっちが好き？",
            "yes": "Summer",
            "left": "夏",
            "no": "Winter",
            "right": "冬"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "What would you do if you found a person in trouble?",
            "jp": "困ってる人がいたらどうする？",
            "yes": "I would help her/him",
            "left": "助ける",
            "no": "I would do nothing",
            "right": "何もしない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Do you think you would love things that you love now if you reborn?",
            "jp": "自分が好きなものを生まれ変わっても好きになる？",
            "yes": "I would definitely love them",
            "left": "絶対に好きになる",
            "no": "I might not love them",
            "right": "ならないかもしれない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "When do you relax more?",
            "jp": "一人でいるときと誰かといるとき、どっちが落ち着く？",
            "yes": "alone",
            "left": "一人",
            "no": "with someone",
            "right": "誰かといるとき"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Do you think youself are an &quot;adult&quot;?",
            "jp": "自分を「大人」だと思っている？",
            "yes": "No i am still a child",
            "left": "まだ子どもだと思っている",
            "no": "Yes i think i am an adult",
            "right": "大人だと思っている"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "Do you feel you are watched over by someone?",
            "jp": "自分は誰かに守られていると感じている？",
            "yes": "Yes / Maybe yes",
            "left": "感じるている、もしくは感じる時がある",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "特に感じない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Are you happy now?",
            "jp": "今、幸せですか？",
            "yes": "I would rather say yes",
            "left": "どちらかといえば幸せ",
            "no": "I would rather say no",
            "right": "どちらかといえば不幸"
        }
    ]
}